(Sheldon:)We have.
(Sheldon:)As a result,
you have taken
(Sheldon:)the most important step
on the road to success:
(Sheldon:)learning what not to do.
(Sheldon:)Now, let's start fresh.
(Sheldon:)Howard, we're going
to need some tea.
(Penny:)Okay, these are Uggs.
(Penny:)These are Crocs.
(Penny:)These are knockoff
Manolo Blahniks.
(Penny:)Bored.
(Penny:)Look, you said it yourself,
we have to create a database
(Penny:)before you can write
an alga-thingy.
(Sheldon:)Algorithm.
(Sheldon:)You see, Penny, Alan Turing
defined an algorithm...
(Penny:)Bored.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Penny:)These are Steve Maddens.
(Penny:)These are Nine West.
(Penny:)These are Target. Oh, but don't
they look like Chanel?
(Penny:)These are
Michael Kors...
♪ Nobody knows... ♪